export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: 'What can we do to protect ourselves?',
        options: ['Wash hands often', 'Go outside and visit a hospital', 'Meet friends without wearing mask'],
        answer: 'Wash hands often'
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Which answer is right about COVID-19?',
        options: ['COVID-19 is not related to respiratory syndrome', 'COVID-19 doesn’t affect anyone in closed space', 'COVID-19 is transmitted by respiratory droplet of an infected person'],
        answer: 'COVID-19 is transmitted by respiratory droplet of an infected person'
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'How long is the period of self-isolated?',
        options: ['1 week', '2 weeks', '3 weeks'],
        answer: '2 weeks'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Who is at higher risk?',
        options: ['normal people', 'Children or older people', 'People with underlying health problems'],
        answer: 'People with underlying health problems'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Where do you have to wear a mask??',
        options: ['When you go for grocery shopping', 'When you are alone at Home', 'Always'],
        answer: 'When you go for grocery shopping'
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What is the official name of coronavirus?',
        options: ['COVID-2019', 'COVID-20', 'COVID-19'],
        answer: 'COVID-19'
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'How many concentrations of alcohol are effective against the virus??',
        options: ['50%', '75%', '99%'],
        answer: '75%'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'How many COVID-19 cases in the world now?',
        options: ['Under 1 million', '1 to 3 million', 'Over 3 millions'],
        answer: 'Over 3 millions'
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Which is the first city shut down due to COVID-19?',
        options: ['Wuhan, China', 'Tokyo, Japa', 'Vancouver, Canada'],
        answer: 'Wuhan, China'
    }
    ,
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Can COVID-19 be cured?',
        options: ['Yes', 'No', 'Depending on the case'],
        answer: 'Depending on the case'
    }
    ,
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Liver injury is usually seen in the liver tissue of COVID-19 patients',
        options: ['True', 'False', 'No idea'],
        answer: 'True'
    }
    ,
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Statistic shows patients with cancer were more likely to develop COVID-19 in China?',
        options: ['True', 'False', 'Cannot tell'],
        answer: 'True'
    }
    ,
    {
        id: 12,
        question: 'What’s the name of the virus that causes COVID-19 in 2020?',
        options: ['SARS-CoV-2', '2019-nCoV', 'SARS-CoV'],
        answer: 'SARS-CoV-2'
    }
    ,
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'Should children wear masks?',
        options: ['Yes', 'No', 'Children under 2 shouldn’t wear masks'],
        answer: 'Children under 2 shouldn’t wear masks'
    }
    ,
    {
        id: 14,
        question: 'Should I inject disinfectant as treatment?',
        options: ['Yes', 'No', 'Trump is right'],
        answer: 'No'
    }
    ,
    {
        id: 15,
        question: 'Need to clean your phone when you arrive home?',
        options: ['Yes', 'No, phone can’t infect me', 'I don’t know'],
        answer: 'Yes'
    }
];